<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MedikalTech</string>
    <string name="app_description">where you can get healthy lifestyle recommendations</string>
    <string name="diabetes_recommendation">
        <b>Healthy Food</b>
        Limit foods that are high in sugar
        <b>Exercise</b>
        30 minutes activities like walk, ride, and jogging
        <b>Lifestyle:</b>
        Manage Stress.
        Stop smoking.
        Watch your alcohol.
    </string>
    <string name="stroke_recommendation">
        <b>Healthy Food:</b>
        Ask your doctor, nurse or a licensed nutritionist or registered dietician for help.
        Be aware of your special needs, especially if you have high blood pressure, high cholesterol or diabetes.
        Avoid foods like fatty meats, butter and cream, which are high in saturated fat.
        Eat moderate amounts of food and cut down on saturated fat, trans fat, sugar and salt.
        Bake, broil, roast and boil foods instead of frying.
        Read nutrition labels on packaged meals. Many are very high in sodium.
        Limit alcohol to one drink a day for women; two drinks per day for men.
        Eat more fruit, vegetables, whole-grains, dried peas and beans, pasta, fish, poultry and lean meats.
        <b>Exercise:</b>
        If you have a chronic medical condition, check with your doctor before you start.
        Start slowly and build up to at least 150 minutes of moderate physical activity (such as brisk walking) a week. Or, you can do 75 minutes of vigorousintensity physical activity, or a combination of the two, to improve overall cardiovascular health.
        Look for even small chances to be more active. Take the stairs instead of an elevator and park farther from your destination.
        <b>Lifestyle:</b>
        Don’t smoke and avoid second-hand smoke.
        Improve your eating habits. Eat foods low in saturated fat, trans fat, sodium and added sugars.
        Be physically active.
        Take your medicine as directed.
        Get your blood pressure checked regularly and work with your healthcare provider to manage it if it’s high.
        Reach and maintain a healthy weight.
        Decrease your stress level.
        Seek emotional support when it’s needed.
        Have regular medical checkups.
    </string>
    <string name="heartdisease_Recommendation">
        <b>Healthy Food:</b>
        Vegetables, fruits, and whole grains; includes low-fat dairy products, poultry, fish, legumes, nontropical vegetable oils, and nuts; and limits intake of sweets, sugar-sweetened beverages, and red meats.
        <b>Exercise:</b>
        150 minutes activity per week exercises like walk, ride, and jogging.
        <b>Lifestyle:</b>
        Stop smoking, manage diabetes, manage stress, limit alcohol.
    </string>
</resources>